(Leonard:)What do you say?
(Sheldon:)I get to write a contract?
(Sheldon:)I say, let's get this party
of the first part started!
(Penny(after Amy laughs):)Do you really think
that's funny?
(Amy:)It's in our agreement.
I have to laugh.
(Sheldon:)If you find this
draft acceptable,
(Sheldon:)then I believe your new
Relationship Agreement
(Sheldon:)is ready to be signed.
Article 8, subsection B:
(Penny:)Leonard will restrict
video-gaming in underpants
(Penny:)to hours Penny is not home.
(Penny:)This includes boxers,
briefs, thongs, G-strings
(Penny:)or anything else
that calls attention
(Penny:)to his pasty little thighs.
(Leonard:)Does it really need to say that?
(Sheldon:)I did this for free,
let me get a little something.
Article 10, subsection C:
(Leonard:)If questioned, Penny
may not say that everything
(Leonard:)is fine if it isn't.
(Leonard:)Other unacceptable responses
include: "It's nothing,"
"Don't worry about it,"
and "I said it's nothing,
don't worry about it."
(Penny:)I think this all looks good.
(Leonard:)Me, too.
(Sheldon:)Oh, well. Great,
then. Here.
(Sheldon:)You sign here, date here.
(Sheldon:)And, Penny, if you could
initial here to indicate
(Sheldon:)that you're accepting Leonard
in "as is" condition.
Aw. I remember signing our first
Relationship Agreement.
(Sheldon:)Mm. You seem to be forgetting
the "no nostalgia" clause.
(Amy:)Right, right. Got it.